goodsie.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Goodsie Ecommerce Software, Online Store Builder

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the type of information that we collect, how Goodsie and other third parties may use this information, and the tracking technologies and processes used to collect it. This policy applies to information we collect when you sign up for Goodsie; access or use our website, products, and services (collectively, the "Services"); or when you otherwise interact with us. This policy also applies to information we collect if you make a purchase at a store hosted on Goodsie using our Services even if you have not signed up for a Goodsie account.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make any material changes to our privacy practices, we will post a revised Privacy Policy here. If you have any questions, please contact us at:

_Goodsie Attention: Privacy Officer 20000 E Country Club Dr. Aventura, FL 33180[Email Privacy Officer](mailto:privacy@goodsie.com)_

### Collection of Information

#### Information You Provide

We collect information you provide, such as when you sign up for a Goodsie account or in the course of a transaction. We may collect, but are not limited to collecting, the following: basic user information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and birth date; financial information, including bank account and payment card numbers; and other contact information. We also collect information when you upload information to the Services about your products and services (including inventory and pricing data) or otherwise communicate with us in customer support forums or by email.

#### Information We Collect from Your Use of the Services

We collect information about how you use our Services, including your access times, browser types and language, and Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses. We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive or in device memory by a website. Among other things, cookies support the integrity of our registration process, retain your preferences and account settings, and help evaluate and compile aggregated statistics about user activity. We may also collect information using web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails. We may use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.

#### Use of Information

We use information about you to provide, maintain, and improve our Services and to deliver the information and support you request, including order receipts, technical notices, service updates, and support and administrative messages.

We may use information we collect to send you news and information about our Services and to communicate with you about products, promotions, incentives, and rewards offered by us and select partners.

We may also use information about you to track and analyze trends and usage in connection with our Services; to protect our rights or property; to verify your identity; to investigate and prevent fraud or other illegal activities; and for any other purpose disclosed to you in connection with our Services.

As part of the buying and selling process on Goodsie, you will obtain the email address and/or shipping address of your customers. By entering into our User Agreement, you agree that, with respect to other users’ Personal Information that you obtain through Goodsie or through a Goodsie-related communication or Goodsie-facilitated transaction, Goodsie hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for Goodsie or commerce related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages. Goodsie does not tolerate spam.

Goodsie may use third party service providers to provide certain services to you and we may share Personal Information with such service providers. We require any company with which we may share Personal Information to protect that data in a manner consistent with this policy and to limit the use of such Personal Information to the performance of services for Goodsie. We do not sell, nor will we ever sell or otherwise provide Personal Information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services.

We may use information we collect in connection with, or during the negotiation of, any merger, sale of company stock or assets, financing, acquisition, divestiture, or dissolution of all or a portion of our business.

We may also use information we collect if we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; to enforce applicable user agreements or policies; to protect the security or integrity of our Services; and to protect us, our users or the public from harm or illegal activities.

#### Information Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number on our account payment form, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Credit card details are stored encrypted using AES-256 encryption. We take all reasonable measures, including administrative, technical, and physical safeguards, to help protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

_Last Updated: 11/14/2013_
